let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: " What is C++?",
        answer: "C. C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
        options: [
            "A. C++ is an object oriented programming language",
            "B. C++ is a procedural programming language",
            "C. C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language",
            "D. C++ is a functional programming language"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "Which of the following approach is used by C++?",
        answer: "C. Bottom-up",
        options: [
            "A. Left-right",
            "B. Right-left",
            "C. Bottom-up",
            "D. Top-down"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "What is virtual inheritance in C++?",
        answer: "D. C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class",
        options: [
            "A. C++ technique to enhance multiple inheritance",
            "B. C++ technique to ensure that a private member of the base class can be accessed somehow",
            "C. C++ technique to avoid multiple inheritances of classes",
            "D. C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "Which of the following type is provided by C++ but not C?",
        answer: "D. bool",
        options: [
            "A.  double",
            "B. float",
            "C. int",
            "D. bool"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: " Which is more effective while calling the C++ functions?",
        answer: "D. call by reference",
        options: [
            "A.call by object",
            "B. call by pointer",
            "C. call by value",
            "D. call by reference"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "What is meant by a polymorphism in C++?",
        answer: "C. class having many forms",
        options: [
            "A. class having only single form",
            "B. class having four forms",
            "C. class having many forms",
            "D. class having two forms"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: " Which of the following is used to terminate the function declaration in C++?",
        answer: "A. ;",
        options: [
            "A. ;",
            "B. ]",
            "C. )",
            "D. :"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: " Which keyword is used to define the macros in c++?",
        answer: "B. #define",
        options: [
            "A. #macro",
            "B. #define",
            "C. macro",
            "D. define"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: " What is Inheritance in C++?",
        answer: "A. Deriving new classes from existing classes",
        options: [
            "A. Deriving new classes from existing classes",
            "B. Overloading of classes",
            "C. Classes with same names",
            "D. Wrapping of data into a single class"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: " What is abstract class in C++?",
        answer: "D. Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one pure virtual functions",
        options: [
            "A. Any Class in C++ is an abstract class",
            "B. Class from which any class is derived",
            "C. Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one virtual functions",
            "D. Class specifically used as a base class with atleast one pure virtual functions"
        ]
    }
]